Hello Vanshvel welcomes you
through this video we will get information
about the features of Digit health insurance plan
in this video we have rated
all the features of Digit health insurance plans
International hospitalization means the
treatment in which you have to stay in the hospital for more than 24 hours In this video international hospitalization means all the
expenses before the day of hospitalization along with the operation are covered in this plan Superintendent of Police
Islamic whatever happens after 90 days of hospitalization
is covered after looking at all the procedures
Domiciliary means any short
stay in hospital even if you are at home due to any reason
hospitals are considered and
domiciliary cover in Digit option six and one
AYUSH board result option C
is teacher cover in 648 AYUSH plan covers all your
Ayurvedic, Naturopathy, Yoga, Unani, Siddha
and Homeopathic treatments
Maternity and Maternity New Born Baby
options are available as cover On this
IS benefit ICU benefit you will
get room rent on the website  You will also get
tax benefit limit on the options.
You get tax benefit under section 80C.
Vaccination cover, worker home,
oxidation cover, escorts, milk will be available in digit option
and option posts will be
available with positive and new porn tower in 108.
Network Hospital Road has more than 6000
network hospitals. Bariatric surgery is a
condition where
excess fat is accumulated in a person's body. It
can have many side effects and
bariatric surgery is used to treat it.
These two digit options
cover up to 5 percent of them.
Inside and audit option it covers up to the
time when cataract surgery is done in all digit
variants. Cataract surgery will be covered after 2 years. That is, the
President of the
hospital of this achievement. How all these three feature options are available as cover
in help areas,
so bottom 0.5 percent of them in short
in your digit option free and courts and
these  Digit Option Seth 0.5% Office Amazon App The
Second Medical Opinion This feature will be
available to you as an optional cover
that a bill a balance picture you will get on the website
Bill Bramble Digit Option is to
stop more on
that your cover is of 5 lakhs then now 50% Option
Mixture Tempo stand for every claim
freers is available i.e. if your coverage is
not for 2 years then your
policy term will be jad khel aap ho jayega
[Music]
A four-digit option 50% for every place
near up to three percent of them informed
cover is the digit option for in 5 percent
for every claim previous is now 25%
term insurance cover is the digit option
six has 20% for every year two hundred
percent of Brahmins who are discovered is the
digit option eight has 50% for every five
years now 200 percent of them in that term is
submit restoration every policy year  In Summit,
100% restoration is given once.
If your total cover gets reduced due to the first claim, then the
plan reverts to 100
% top basic cover.
This facility is available to you once in every policy series. In
Plan Mode of Three, one time restoration
up to 100% in policy means one
digit option for one time
restoration and two digit option for
unlimited restoration for those who are less than 40 years
and one time restoration for those who are more than 40 years. There will be
waiting period in which
some specific diseases like
treatment of cancer and ligaments,
joint replacement, transplant surgery, or other
system diseases like diabetes, cancer,
heart related conditions, extra waiting
period of 3 years, old age option for free and
24 digit, 2 digit option and fixed and
121 effect. Go to your home page and gain
knowledge about insurance in One Star Academy.